# Vedabrat Etwaru

## CEO at TechIT

vedabrat@gmail.com

# Summary

Experienced automation and full stack web developer. Rails, C#, Javascript, AngularJS, Node, HTML, CSS, jQuery languages and Linux and Windows systems. Excel Guru. Well versed and intuitive in finance. Versed in System Administration, Architecture, and Networking.

# Experience

# Web Developer

June 2013 - Present

Maintaining TechIT's web presence, as well as many other sites listed below.

# Web Developer

November 2017 - Present

I maintain the webspace and any requests that www.ambotautomation.com requests.

## Arbitrage Analyst

February 2015 - July 2015 (6 months)

- -Budget Analysis and projections/forecasting
- -Bank, Escrow, and Account reconciliation
- -Annual & Supplemental Debt Statement and Statement Of Indebtedness prep
- -Operating Statement creation for Bond Ordinance
- -Debt (Bond, BAN, TAN, SEN) Analysis and Refunding
- -PILOT, Retrograde-Salary, and Tax Levy analysis
- -Budget Reversion Study. (Calendar Year Fiscal Year Analysis)
- -Time Report Management

## **Procurement Manager**

January 2012 - October 2014 (2 years 10 months)

- -Billing, shipping, warehouse inventory, order management
- -Sent out weekly reports (COGS) and customized reports (SQL and otherwise) as requested
- -Policy Manager between sales and operations departments
- -Costing Management and Data Entry for royalties and licensed goods/information
- -Developed, implemented and tested an automation system for order entry (65% reduction in employee time/resources.)
- -Administrative Management of the supply and procurement of on hand goods

- -Data Infrastructure Advisor
- -Trained new hires

#### **Executive Assistant**

# June 2011 - December 2011 (7 months)

- -Analyze/reconcile revenue and expense accounts.
- -Provided satisfactory customer service by receiving, analyzing, researching and seeking resolutions to assigned inquiries
- -Organized, managed and updated customer databases for staff reports
- -Prepared weekly & monthly payroll and management information reports
- -Prepared Food Program forms and vouchers for program compliance with the Board of Ed
- -Miscellaneous daily issues management
- -Prepared and updated client personal profile.
- -Organized conferences with Mayors, Directors within the Board of Ed., and local parishes.

#### **Technical Assistant**

# May 2006 - February 2011 (4 years 10 months)

- Technical Engineer. Installed and Troubleshooted Networks, PCs, devices, and software in corporate workspaces
- -Managed email accounts, phone systems, installed network cables, edited customer profile databases, organization schedules, set up and repaired POS systems.
- -Conducted and managed sales orders and billing.
- -Strategic Financial Position&Leverage Analyst .
- -Synced mobile devices to workstations and live networks.

# Education

# 2011 Rutgers University

Bachelor of Science Degree, Finance, 2005 - 2011

Bloc

Full Stack Web Developer, Web Development, 2017 - 2018

Activities and Societies: Slack, StackOverflow, Reddit, BlocStudents, Frontend

2004 Hudson County

High school Diploma, Computer Science and Drama, 2001 - 2004

# Vedabrat Etwaru

# **CEO** at TechIT

vedabrat@gmail.com



Contact Vedabrat on LinkedIn